You're right, the party's fantastic!
Tell me more.
(Howard:)I haven't heard enough about it,
because hearing about that never gets old!
- Is this about the space thing again?
- I'm not allowed to talk about it...
(Howard:)...but since you brought it up,
I went to space. Space, space, space!
Oh, Drinky Smurf!
(Bernadette:)- Can I talk to you for a second?
- Great, now I'm in trouble.
(Howard:)You happy?
(Bernadette:)You, out!
(Bernadette:)You are being very rude.
(Howard:)No I'm not. They're all being rude,
and you're being rude.
(Bernadette:)Me? What did I do?
"Oh, Howie,
stop talking about space so much."
"Nobody likes it."
(Bernadette(in a gruff voice):)I don't sound like that.
(Howard:)You're supposed to be on my side.
(Bernadette:)I'm always on your side.
(Howard:)Then why are you trying to
take this away from me?
(Howard:)Being an astronaut is the coolest thing
I'm ever going to do...